moviesinsight.com 2019-08-14

# Privacy Policy - Movies Insight

We appreciate your trust with our website. The submission of your personal information is not at all required in order to browse website but there can be changes in the policies. To stay updated keep checking for them. By visiting the website you assure that you accept all the privacy policies described in this notice.

## What personal information do we gather?

Whatever information that we receive from users helps us provide you an enhanced improvement of your experience at the website. Here is the information that we accumulate:

  * Automatic Information: We receive and store several types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, many websites use “Cookies” and obtain a certain type of information when you access the website on the web browser or other content served by on behalf of the website on other websites.
  * The information you provide us: We store any information that you enter on our website. We use the information just to respond to your requests, improving our website and communication with you.
  * Other websites links: The content on this website may contain links to other external websites. Once you will click on such links they will redirect you to other websites. Please acknowledge the fact that we do not have any control over those particular website(s).

## What are cookies?

When you use your browser in order to visit or surf any website usually small text files can place themselves in your computer as browser’s history or program data subfolders which are called Cookies. A cookie can be of two types- the first is which expires when you close the browser and the second stays in your computer until you delete it manually. So like another company our readers will get cookies by us or by companies which are running their ads on our website. Cookies can help us and advertisers to analyze and identify users on our website and it also helps us to serve content to match your preferences.

## Do we share your personal information?

Information about our users is very important for us and we do not disclose that information to someone else. We only share it in the following instances:

  * In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation of the our terms and provisions
  * To implement or entail terms and conditions and privacy policies
  * To protect our character, assets and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users
  * We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law to do so in a good belief because it is necessary to disclose such info to counter court orders or miscellaneous legal processes.
  * In case of transferring or selling the website to other company so user’s info will be transferred too. We may disclose non-identifiable data to third parties which don't include your name, email address or contact number.

## Third party advertisements:

We have advertising companies advertising with. We do not share any personal information with them. These companies work on their behalf; they automatically receive your IP address because of which you receive their advertisements on your browser. They might also use cookies, java scripts, web beacons and other technologies to measure the efficiency of their ads and modify their content.
